teladoc.com 2019-12-21

# Teladoc Health

_Effective: July 1, 2019_

### Introduction

Teladoc Health Inc., on its own behalf and on behalf of its affiliates and/or wholly owned subsidiaries including but not limited to Best Doctors, Inc., Best Doctors Canada, Inc., HealthiestYou, Inc., and Teladoc Physicians, P.A. (collectively referred to as “Teladoc Health”, “we”, “us”, or “our”), owns and operates the websites located at www.teladoc.com, www.bestdoctors.com, www.askbestdoctors.com, members.bestdoctors.com, www.healthiestyou.com, www.teladochealth.com, www.teladoc.ca, member.teladoc.com, partner.healthiestyou.com, member.healthiestyou.com, client.healthiestyou.com and various mobile applications (collectively, the “Website” or “Websites”). Through these Websites we offer various online services that enable visitors to the Websites (“you” or “Visitors”) to receive access to various types of healthcare information and information about our services (“Services”). 

Teladoc understands that privacy of information is of great importance to our Visitors. 

### Applicability of this privacy policy

This Web and Mobile Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) describes what information Teladoc Health collects about Visitors on the publicly available portions of the Websites and how that information is used.

### Agreement to this privacy policy

Your access and use of the Websites is subject to your agreement with this Privacy Policy and the Web and Mobile Terms and Conditions. By using the Website, you expressly agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and consent to the collection and use of information as discussed in this Privacy Policy.  
If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not use or access the Websites for any purpose. Please print a copy of this Privacy Policy for your records.

### Modifications to this privacy policy

Teladoc Health may revise this Privacy Policy regarding the collection of information at any time. Should this Privacy Policy change materially, Teladoc Health will give notice to you by posting a notice regarding the new policy on the Websites. The revised Privacy Policy will be effective as of its posting unless otherwise stated.

By accessing or using the Website after such changes are posted you agree to all such changes.

### Collection use and disclosure of non identifiable information

Either Teladoc Health or a third party vendor on behalf of Teladoc Health may automatically collect information while Visitors browse the Websites. We may collect such information by tracking, or asking a third party vendor to track, your click-stream activity when such information is not tied to a user ID through the use of "cookie" technology or by tracking internet protocol (IP) addresses, as explained below.

Because we want our Websites to better serve Visitors’ needs, we collect some basic information about Visitors and their devices, including, but not limited to:

  * IP address (the computer’s address on the Internet)
  * Operating system (e.g. Windows Vista)
  * Browser software (e.g. Microsoft Internet Explorer, Firefox)
  * Internet Service Provider (e.g. AOL)
  * Geographic location (e.g. Boston, Mass.)
  * Type of device (e.g. iPad, desktop)
  * Mobile device crash information
  * Locale and language of device and whether it has fingerprint/face sensors
  * Dates and time you accessed and used the Website, features you used in the Website, and how long you use the Website overall
  * Links you click and pages you view within the Website
  * Pages you view before and after you leave the Website

We use this information to continuously enhance our Websites and to better serve our Visitors’ needs. For example, we use this information to know what browsers people most commonly use, what pages are most often visited, and what functionality is most used. Some of the information we collect from Visitors, such as IP Address, may be considered identifiable personal information (“Personal Information”). Additionally, there are times on our Website that Visitors are able to voluntarily submit Personal Information, such as their name, phone number, and/or email address in order to obtain more information from Teladoc Health. We may remove personal identifiers from your Personal Information and maintain and use it in a de-identified form (“De-Identifiable Information”). De-Identifiable Information and Personal Information are collectively referred to throughout this Privacy Policy as “Information”.

The Information collected from Visitors on our Websites may be shared with our suppliers and vendors and used in the aggregate to create summary statistics that help us analyze the Websites’ usage trends, assess what information is of most and least importance, determine technical design specifications, arrange the Websites in the most user-friendly way, and identify system performance or problem areas.

By continuing to use the Websites, you hereby consent to the use and disclosure of your Information as set forth below:

  * within Teladoc or with our service providers such as a cloud service provider in Canada or the United States for data storage; 
  * with our financial, insurance, legal, accounting or other advisors that provide professional services to us;
  * to respond to a subpoena, order, legal process, or government request;
  * to protect, establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;
  * to investigate, detect, suppress, prevent or take action regarding illegal or prohibited activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the reputation or physical safety of any person;
  * if we are to be sold, merged, or amalgamated or substantially all of our assets are to be sold or disposed of, your personal information may be transferred to a potential purchaser if, and to the extent necessary, it is required for the purposes of deciding whether to proceed with the proposed transaction and completing it. If such a sale, merger, acquisition, or disposal is completed, we will use reasonable efforts to direct the transferee to use personal information you have provided to us in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy. Following such a sale or transfer, you may contact the entity to which we transferred your personal information with any inquiries concerning the processing of that information; or
  * as otherwise required by law.

### Cookies

Like many companies, we use “cookies” to help you better navigate the Websites. A “cookie” is a small piece of information sent by Teladoc Health’s web-based applications that are stored by your web browser on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies enhance your online experience by saving your preferences while you are visiting a particular Website. The cookies do not contain any identifiable information and cannot profile your system or collect information from your hard drive. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can set your browser to refuse them or to alert you when they are being sent.

For more information about the cookies that are used on the Websites and your ability to opt out of use of those cookies, please see Teladoc Health’s Cookies Policy.

### YOUR RIGHTS REGARDING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

**Amendment.** You have a right to request that Teladoc amend or delete the Personal Information it collects from your use of the Websites if you believe it is incorrect or incomplete, and you may request an amendment or deletion for as long as the Personal Information is retained by Teladoc. You must submit your request in writing to Teladoc and provide a reason to support the requested amendment. Teladoc may, under certain circumstances, deny your request by sending you a written notice of denial.

**Withdrawal of Consent.** Subject to applicable law, you may withdraw your consent to uses and disclosures of Personal Information as outlined in this Privacy Policy. You must submit your request in writing to Teladoc. Withdrawing consent does not invalidate consent to any collection, use or disclosure of Personal Information to which you consented before consent was withdrawn. If you withdraw consent, or refuse further consent, Teladoc’s ability to offer services to you may be limited.

### How to contact us?

Questions or comments regarding this Policy should be submitted to the Teladoc Health Privacy Officer by mail or electronic means as follows:

Teladoc Privacy Officer  
Teladoc Health, Inc.  
2 Manhattanville Road, Suite 203  
Purchase, NY 10577
